how you doing I'm Justin with audio and
vision we're a home theater installation
company here in Mesa Arizona today I
want to talk to you about the Bose sound
touch 10 uh the reason I'm I'm talking
about this speaker is because it kind of
surprised me some of the features of it
and was kind of it was really cool um
compared to some some other brands I
deal with which is Sonos hios and uh
pulk audio wireless Bluetooth speakers
so let me tell you about why this
speaker is cool uh it's wireless speaker
and it supports WiFi and Bluetooth so
the reason that's important is because
most of the speakers out there fall into
two categories Wi-Fi and Bluetooth and
Bluetooth speakers are cool because you
can take them anywhere you can take him
to a hotel room on
vacation uh to your friend's house to
play music or like I do I take this guy
to my job sites a lot of the times I'm
installing the sound system so there
isn't one to actually play music music
on while I'm working this guy makes it
fun uh so that's a Bluetooth speaker
very versatile it's a direct connection
between your phone and the speaker a
wi-fi speaker is a little bit different
uh they're more for uh whole home audio
Wi-Fi speakers can connect to each other
to form one big sound system in your
home or you can separate the speakers to
form smaller little sound systems in
your home as you wish you can con
combine them and separate them whenever
you want uh so if I had another one of
these downstairs like a Bose sound touch
20 I could combine them together and
they'd both be playing the same music
for my phone at the same time if I
wanted to take it with me to say Vegas
and just have a little music in my hotel
room I could also do that and not have
to worry about their Network or their
Wi-Fi uh at the hotel room because it's
a Bluetooth connection it's directly
between the phone and the speaker so uh
let's talk about some of the benefits of
the this guy it's a really good speaker
it's light lightweight um easy to carry
around it's powered it has to be plugged
into the wall it does not have a battery
on it it has something that I've never
seen before on any other speaker which
is this little presets all right so this
is a screenshot of my phone I can show
you what I'm doing so the sound Touch
app right there is what I'm going to
select and I already downloaded it so
you can get that on iTunes or Google
play um once you download it you need to
create an account a Bose account which
I've done already and what's kind of
cool is uh one of the things I noticed
is if I go to internet radio it ask for
my ZIP code when I created the account
now what it did with that information is
it just gave me some of local stations
that are already here in my area that's
cool and also you can just go down to
Global and select any station that you
like in the world so that's cool local
radio stations I'll play one for you
let's go to
93.3 there we go
so turn it
up if I was not doing AirPlay by the way
I would be able to turn up volume using
my
phone so we got that now what if I
wanted to always listen to this station
well if you remember back in the old
days the old cars that had the little
button that you pressed to hold the
radio station on um it's the same thing
you press the one
press and hold it makes a sound and now
that station is programmed into the
preset on number one so I can come back
to it anytime and press number one
without using my phone and listen to
that station same thing applies for if
you go up here to I have Pandora Pandora
account and I have a couple favorite
stations I like to listen to so let's
pull up this one so we have a music
playing this is a Pandora station and go
ahead and press the UN hold the number
two and it's programmed so now anytime I
want I can go back
to what was that
93.3 there we
go and then I want to go back to P
Gabriel on Pandora I can press
that it makes it really really easy to
use sometimes I don't want to have to
bust out my phone to just play some
music on the speaker uh it also
functions as just a standalone Bluetooth
speaker so let's try that
out so I press the input button right
here and it's on Bluetooth is
highlighted okay so I'm connected to
sound touch 10 I don't know if you can
see
that and I'm going to go ahead and open
up a Pandora app on my phone here we
go there we go so now I'm I'm connected
Bluetooth from my phone to the speaker
Wi-Fi is not in involved at all I could
I could take this over to uh my friend's
house or to a hotel room or if I have a
generator if I have a camper uh you
could put it in there as well and it's
using the LTE connection on my phone
right now uh my phone's not even on
Wi-Fi so very versatile speaker awesome
to have I love it it's got a great sound
uh really deep base you can see the base
port on the back and uh it just
resonates really well and I'm really
happy with it I'll probably be getting
some more here in the future um thank
you and this is my review on the bow
sound touch 10 uh coming back and see my
other reviews I'll be doing Apple TV uh
remote controls video switchers just you
know any product I have lyed around so
uh I'm Justin with audio and vision and
again we're home theater company here in
Mesa Arizona give us a call if you need
our help thanks